## Rajab Bobomuratov



### **Junior Front-end Developer**

I'm a React Front-end developer with experience in UX/UI design and knowledge of QA Manual.

I completed a course on JavaScript and React development, with a significant emphasis on self-study.

During my studies, I tried to use additional technologies that were not included in the course plan.

I have also been working on / continue to work on:

- · Ameliance UI a library that I used for personal tasks and as the main UI library in one of the final team tasks;
- · Ameliance Scripts is an npm scripting library that I move specific functions or functions that I use frequently to;
- · RS School - Telegram bot for school chat, written in Telegraf and later rewritten by grammY;
- · A set of api functions written in Google Apps Script a pseudo-backend for working with Google Sheets via the REST API.

In team tasks, I was a team leader, setting up projects, organizing processes and communication.

During the course, I received the status of "rs-activists" for helping other students and moderating a Ukrainian-language chat on Telegram.

Throughout my studies, I kept notes in notion, which turned into a mini encyclopedia that is sometimes used by close classmates or people who know about it.

I also have non-commercial / semicommercial experience in developing scripts and tools in JS (Figma, After Effects, Studio One), Lua (Reaper DAW), AHK (Windows OS) and some other languages.

I love to experiment and am always in the process of learning something new. Furthermore, I am not afraid to use new approaches and change my habits if I see logic and growth for myself.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Junior UX/UI Designer

APR 2021 - JUL 2021 // unqa.agency (agency, Rivne)

Web design, corporate identity and logo design

Presentation of projects to the customer

#### **Graphic Designer**

DEC 2011 - JAN 2015 // Bureau MarT (advertising consulting agency, Rivne)

Logos design, corporate styles, outdoor advertising, printed and souvenir products

#### **EDUCATION**

### React

SEP 2022 - DEC 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

React, Redux Toolkit, React API. 6 tasks, including a team task

### JavaScript/Front-end

MAR 2022 - SEP 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School Core JavaScript, TypeScript, layout, algorithms, development under the

supervision of a mentor. More than 7 projects, including a team task

I tried to use it myself: React, Redux (vanilla), Axios, Lottie animation, Web Animations API, etc. During the course, I created my own UI library and scripting library, which I used in all assignments

# **JS/FE Pre-School**

DEC 2021 - MAR 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

Preparatory course for JavaScript/Front-end

During the course, we learned the basic basics of JS, HTML, CSS, and git. We tried to develop our own website, game, and work with RestAPI. Over than 5 personal projects

# **UX Design**

2021 // bangbangeducation

A video course on interface design

# **Basics of QA Manual**

AUG 2021 - AUG 2022 // QATestLab

A month-long course on the basics of QA manual testing

### 2019 // WDIR

**UX/UI** Design

A video course on web and interface design. Everything from working with a

client to the finished design

# **PROJECTS**

### AW O >

React, TypeScript, Redux, SCSS Modules, Vite, ESLint, Autoprefixer, Firebase, React Hook Form,

Ameliance UI, Ameliance Scripts, React Responsive, React Router DOM, React Showfall, Google Apps

Script

Pet Project Single Page Application for use within a music group. The application

contains a list of songs, chords, and a chat for communication. The app's

functionality includes the ability to create a song list and transpose chords The project was started at the beginning of my studies in vanilla JavaScript and later rewritten in React. Some of the functionality is in the process of

# More projects

being ported to React

on the web version of CV →

on github →

#### Message me on Telegram

**Location:** Rivne, remote **Phone:** +380 (97) 123 57 33

Telegram: <a>@amelianceskymusic</a>

E-mail: radzhab@ukr.net

**GitHub:** github.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com

### **HARD SKILLS**

React, Next.js

TypeScript, JavaScript

Redux / RTK, Zustand

HTML

CSS / SCSS / SCSS Modules

MUI, Mantine, Tailwind

Vite, Webpack, Create React App

ESLint / Prettier

Git / GitHub

React Hook Form

React Router Dom

Rest API

#### **Others**

Visual Studio Code

Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

Json, Yaml, Ini

Notion, Jira, Slack

Handwrite

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Adaptability

Critical thinking

Focus on results

Friendly

Honesty

Perfectionism

Stress tolerance

Self-development

### **LANGUAGES**

### **English**

Αl

## **Polish**

Αl

# **Ukrainian**

Native

#### Russian Unfortunately, I know

# **HOBBIES**

instruments and compose music In my free time I like to write

I am musician. I play musical

code, automate routine tasks, ride a bike